Teachers Union of the City of New York Additional Records 5927
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Teachers Union of the City of New York Additional Records
1931-1937
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Teachers Union of the City of New York
5927
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
The collection consists of a few folders of photocopies of miscellaneous documents, including convention proceedings, rank and file meetings, speeches, and pamphlets produced by the union. Most material spans the 1930s.
5734541
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 08, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of a few folders of photocopies of miscellaneous documents, including convention proceedings, rank and file meetings, speeches, and pamphlets produced by the union. Most material spans the 1930s.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5015: Teachers Union of the City of New York Records 5445: Teachers Union of the City of New York Records
Teachers' unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Teachers' Union of the City of New York.
5734541
- American League Against War and Fascism, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Rank and File Meetings, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Rank and File Meetings - Academic Freedom Tenure, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Unemployed Teachers, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Teachers Unions, 1931-1937 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Executive Board Meetings 1933 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Executive Board Meetings 1933 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 1934 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Henry/Hans Linvill/Linville, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Rank and File Group in the Teachers Union, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Rank and File & other Union Papers, 1932-1934 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Mimeographing, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 12)